Kathy Church

Software Developer at CSG International

kathy.church@gmail.com

Summary

I am a Software Developer in Atlanta for CSG Invotas, a software company focused on Cyber Security automation and orchestration solutions. In this role, I have worked on the core product and also developed plugins for numerous third party security devices and services. Our most recent exciting work was the debut of Invotas Security Orchestrator 3.0 at the RSA conference in February. Before joining the Invotas group, I worked in CSG Government Solutions for 6 years, working on customized solutions that meet the specific challenges of clients in the Federal Government. Prior to that, I worked for Harris Corporation in Florida on embedded systems projects and robotics simulations. I am a software developer with over 10 years experience in the Atlanta area who has been working in Python since 2008. I am currently wrapping up a Front-end Development Nanodegree from Udacity.com where I have learned JavaScript and many front-end development tools. I am really looking forward to putting my new skills to work! I have a BS in Computer Science from Georgia Institute of Technology. I love hearing from former colleagues and interesting people, so feel free to contact me if you'd like to connect.

Experience

Software Developer at CSG International

2011 - Present (4 years)

Developer for the Invotas Security Orchestrator product

Software Engineer at Intec

December 2007 - 2011 (4 years)

Coordinated with interdisciplinary teams to design and implement solutions using Intec's products for clients in the Federal Government.

Software Engineer at Harris Corporation

2006 - 2008 (2 years)

Worked as a software engineer on a variety of projects: - Developing testing interfaces for embedded systems - Analysis and corrections for solving errors in high speed network traffic - Developing a 3D environment for robotics simulation in Microsoft Robotics Studio

Contractor at Verizon Business

May 2006 - December 2006 (8 months)

Consulted to produce documentation and enhancement suggestions for their billing analysis system.

Software Engineer at Intec

May 2004 - April 2006 (2 years)

Coordinated with interdisciplinary teams including customers, project managers, and other developers to design and implement solutions for customers using Intec's mediation system.

Skills & Expertise

XML

Unix

Python

Software Development

Software Design

JavaScript

Front-end Development

Testing

Requirements Analysis

Linux

Integration

Solution Architecture

Shell Scripting

Software Engineering

Databases

System Architecture

Software Documentation

Scrum

Web Applications

Programming

Database Design

Unix Shell Scripting

Object Oriented Design

Subversion

Architectures

Github

C#

UML

Education

Udacity

Nanodegree, Front-End Web Developer, 2014 - 2015

Georgia Institute of Technology

BS, Computer Science, 2000 - 2004

Chattahoochee High School

1996 - 2000

Kathy Church

Software Developer at CSG International

kathy.church@gmail.com



Contact Kathy on LinkedIn